Hollywood is a killer.
MaXXXine is a horror, thriller film directed by Ti West.
In 1980s Hollywood, adult film star and aspiring actress
Maxine Minx finally gets her big break.
But as a mysterious killer stalks the starlets of Hollywood, a
trail of blood threatens to reveal her sinister past.
Maxine Minx, played by Mia Goth.
Elizabeth Bender, played by Elizabeth Debicki.
Leon, played by Moses Sumney.
Detective Williams, played by Michelle Monaghan.
Detective Torres, played by Bobby Cannavale.
Tabby Martin, played by Halsey.
MaXXXine is a 2024 American slasher film written,
directed, produced, and edited by Ti West.
It is the third and final installment in West's X
trilogy and a direct sequel to X (2022).
Mia Goth reprises her role as Maxine Minx, starring alongside Elizabeth Debicki, Moses Sumney, Michelle
Monaghan, Bobby Cannavale, Halsey, Lily Collins, Giancarlo Esposito, and Kevin Bacon.
In the film, Maxine sets out for fame and success in 1980s
Hollywood while being targeted by a mysterious killer.
MaXXXine had its premiere at the TCL Chinese Theatre in Los Angeles on June 24,
2024, and was released in the United States by A24 on July 5, 2024.
The film grossed $22 million worldwide, becoming the
highest-grossing film of the series.
The film explores themes of pornography, gore, sequel, murder, fame.
The tone is dark and intense.